Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Shake him.
♪ Black smoke
And heavy eyes ♪
♪ False hope and alibis… ♪
♪ A poisoned lullaby… ♪
♪ Dark shadows in the sky… ♪
Shit.
♪ The secrets and the lies ♪
-♪ This night is our disguise… ♪
-This way. ma'am.
♪ The words between the lines ♪
♪ Consume me from inside… ♪
♪ They're burned into my mind… ♪
♪ There's nowhere left to hide ♪
♪ And now we must decide… ♪
♪ How we will live or die… ♪
♪ Hold your breath ♪
♪ We're not turning back ♪
Hey.
-Just call me later. yeah?
-Yes. Yeah.
-What's going on?
-We need to talk.
Prime Minister.
General Livingston.
As Chief of the Defence Staff.
you should know that I ordered MI6
to locate four doctors
being held hostage in French Guiana.
Uh… I know that breaks normal protocol.
but President Toussaint authorized
and then aborted a French rescue mission.
I gave our agent on the ground permission
to pursue the two Jeeps
that the doctors were loaded into.
-I've kept it close.
-May I ask why?
One of the hostages is my husband.
I'm being blackmailed.
Someone sent me a video
of us in Washington.
-Did you share it with anyone?
-Are you really asking me that?
No. Listen. I'm… I'm sorry.
Fuck.
What do they even want?
-They're demanding Dalton's resignation.
-Jesus.
I know we don't have
a significant presence in the area.
but there must be other rescue scenarios.
Black ops team?
Air support for any kind of British
mission would take 48 hours to mobilize.
and even then. sending our military
into a French territory
would be impossible to hide.
Hmm. You'd need Toussaint's clearance.
What made her pull the mission?
We were about
to send in a rescue team.
but they threatened to go public
with the video. so I… I called it off.
Get Secret Service to trace the message.
Shut them down.
I can't have anyone who works for me
know about us.
They have her husband. For Christ's sake.
you have to do something.
They took him on French soil.
They're controlling my response.
so I can't help her.
Right now.
I… I don't even know who to trust.
Then you shouldn't have come here.
It's too much of a risk.
I don't have anyone else
to talk to about this. I…
You know what's at stake here if Desmaris
and his far-right thugs take power.
I have to win the election.
You cannot let them do this to you.
Help me.
Even if you were able
to buy us the two days we need.
I can't promise that we can keep
this mission a secret from the French.
Then I have to convince Toussaint
to change her mind.
There's someone I know.
they could take a look at your phone.
One of the people you protest with?
They wanna see me buried.
But I don't. Vivienne. listen to me.
I'm on that video too.
Uh. give me a few hours.
Vivienne. it's Abigail.
We've been over all the rescue scenarios.
There's no way of bringing them back alive
without your help.
Whatever's happened. whatever's going on.
we need to keep talking.
I'm… I'm running out of time.
Slow him down.
Stop!
Why didn't you kill him?
In French. for fuck's sake.
Carol from Birmingham.
Carol. you're live on air.
Tell us your story.
My husband was diagnosed
with Hodgkin's lymphoma in January.
Oh.
He's been responding well to the chemo.
but three weeks ago
they told us they couldn't source
a supply of medication for him.
He's been going downhill ever since.
We've been trying everywhere.
but all the patient liaison officers
we speak to say they're out of stock.
And he can't wait any longer.
He's just getting worse.
He's 48 years old.
and without chemo. he's gonna die.
You know. I voted for this government.
for Abigail Dalton.
because she said
she was gonna put the NHS first.
But what's the use of more nurses
if they don't have enough drugs?
Morning. all. Shall we?
-Would you mind?
-Ahem.
Where the fuck is Toussaint?
She's ignoring my calls.
Mercer is missing.
MI6 located his truck via satellite.
They found blood but no body.
-Even so. we have to assume he's dead.
-So what do we do now?
The kidnappers will reach out again.
The deadline is 1:00 pm.
And that's it? We just… we just wait?
We can attempt
to de-escalate the situation
and appeal for a peaceful release.
but you cannot negotiate.
You need to neutralize the power
they have over you.
By letting Alex die?
By choosing your country over your family.
That's the job.
Tell the Cabinet. They need to know.
No. It will undermine my authority
in the middle of a national crisis.
The longer you keep this a secret.
the worse it'll be when the news gets out.
You have to tell your ministers.
Is the deal possible
with President Toussaint?
Not unless we're willing
to let the French immigration officers
enforce UK borders.
She's trying to secure a deal
that appeals to the hard right.
We're a sovereign nation.
-We police our own borders.
-That's exactly what I told her.
-If she's immovable--
-Prime Minister.
You simply can't
allow the French to dictate terms.
We're already getting it in the neck
from the Mail for taking in the migrants--
Refugees.
-Right. Look. uh. I'm simply saying--
-It's noted. Dan. Thank you.
There's. uh. rumors circling Whitehall
that Toussaint left the reception
rather abruptly last night.
Is there something else going on
we should know. Prime Minister?
Nothing that's relevant
to this conversation.
What's next?
Sylvie. you shouldn't.
That's classified.
You shouldn't even be in here. Uh…
I know about the deadline.
That they're going to kill someone.
-I'm so sorry. I didn't know she was here.
-It's not Ayesha's fault. You lied to me.
You said as soon as you knew anything.
you'd tell me.
-We were just trying to verify a location.
-Bullshit!
Don't talk to me like that.
Ayesha…
-Just give me a second.
-Yeah. of course.
What happened?
There was a French rescue team en route.
and then President Toussaint
changed her mind about sending them--
-Why would she do that?
-I… I don't know.
What do they want from you?
They want me to stand down.
So you're gonna have to do that.
They took him
because they think that I will give in
if it comes down to a choice
between this job and my family.
But they don't know who I am. who we are.
Your dad was with me
every step of the way to get here.
He wouldn't want me to surrender.
Not until we were out of options.
You can put any kind of spin on it
you want.
but if anything happens to Dad.
I'll never forgive you.
Who is he?
Must be MI6.
He came to rescue us.
-I need your help.
-Mm-hmm.
Okay. He's lost quite a bit of blood
front and back.
Trace. search the med kit
for Celox. HemCon. and an IV.
Hey. Hey. I'm Alex.
We're doctors. Can you tell us your name?
-It's Tom. Tom.
-Hey. Tom.
-Yeah.
-Right. We're gonna help you. okay?
I've got Celox. but no fluids though.
Find the exit wound
on the back. right?
-Apply as much pressure as you can.
-Got it.
Celox.
Tom. this is gonna hurt. okay?
Phew.
-Stay with us. Tom.
-You're all right.
Did you hear them?
They're British. What does that mean?
It means that someone's gone
to a lot of trouble to get rid of my wife.
Bonjour.
Mmm.
-What are you doing?
-Ah!
Hey.
-Someone's following me.
-What?
The men from last night.
-Wh… what? Which men? What. Sas?
-When I left your place.
Your… your stepmum's security.
I see one of them now.
-Why is she doing this to me?
-Uh. no… It's all right. You're okay.
No. no. no. It's not all right.
First she comes to your flat
at fucking 3:00 a.m.. and now this.
There's something you're not
telling me. isn't there?
Who is this woman?
Uh. me and Vivienne
were in a relationship.
-What?
-It didn't last long. but it… it was real.
She's your fucking stepmum.
Uh. how?
I worked for a few weeks
on her campaign. and. um…
It was… it was crazy and intense.
and I think. in a weird way.
we maybe needed each other.
This is some fucked-up thing
to do with your dad. right?
Look. I'm not making any excuses.
and I did feel something.
but it's in the past.
Sas.
I love you.
And I really need you.
You have to believe that.
Prime Minister.
I'll be in the car.
Look. I couldn't tell the Cabinet.
not yet. I need more time.
-To do what?
-To make a deal with Toussaint.
I'm going to speak to her at this event.
I have to convince her to change her mind.
The mission was set.
then she backed out. and I wanna know why.
She's playing hardball
to try and win an election.
If I give her what she wants.
maybe she'll help me bring Alex back.
You heard Ogilvy. The knives will be out
the moment you make
a concession on our border security.
-It's all she's interested in discussing.
-I'll negotiate.
You are badly compromised. This is
why you have to tell your ministers.
-No one in your position--
-No one is in my position.
Prime Minister.
I cannot serve you
if you won't take my advice.
For Christ's sake. Kofi. How many fronts
do you want me to be fighting on?
I am not fighting you.
I have been trying to help you.
But by continuing down this path.
you leave me no alternative.
You're going to quit
in the middle of all of this?
I have 22 years on the clock
and a reputation I am damn proud of.
but it's clear
my counsel is of no use to you.
I know you've been shopping around
for my replacement.
so maybe you'd like
to expedite that process.
Has the French president outplayed you.
Prime Minister?
Prime Minister!
It's day two
of the crucial Anglo-French summit.
and PM Abigail Dalton
and French president Vivienne Toussaint
are attending the Electric Vehicle Exhibit
in central London.
one of several public appearances
they will be making over the coming days.
Prime Minister Dalton is set
to negotiate a number of issues
with President Toussaint…
A collaboration that transcends borders.
driving us towards a sustainable future.
This aircraft is powered entirely
by electric motors…
I've been calling your people all morning.
We need to talk.
Not here.
It has to be now. I'm out of time.
Now. these are
a fairly fascinating piece of kit.
Basically. you're charging
from one battery to another.
If I allow you
to put your border forces on UK soil.
it will ruin me politically.
…technology is that it can be deployed
absolutely anywhere.
Isn't that right?
-But I have no choice.
-Also fantastic is its focus.
It's wonderful. Now…
-I'll do it.
-When you consider 95%…
I'll give you what you want.
if that's what it takes.
…normal charging. but you are right…
I can't.
-What do you mean?
-…the bigger problems…
It's what you came here for.
-You want the bloody deal. Take it.
-…and logistics. not technology.
How do you address the challenge
of reducing the charging time?
The efficiency of the process is paramount
for its widespread adoption. no?
Indeed. that is a crucial aspect
of our electric revolution.
If you want to humiliate me
and score points back home. that's fine.
Just
help me bring him home.
…plenty of time for charging…
I'm begging you.
No. Bigger problems around charging
are political and logistical…
If this isn't a negotiation tactic.
then… why did you stop the mission?
Madam President.
how's your trip in London?
I want you in that situation room with me
when the deadline expires.
because if any of those doctors die.
then their blood will be on your hands.
That is going to be a problem
we are hoping to address in the future.
-Thank you so much. It has been…
-Thank you.
…such a pleasure to meet you both.
-Thank you very much.
-Pleasure.
Madam President!
That dress with the
pockets hasn't fitted her for two years.
Because you never throw anything out.
I need to see her.
Tell me that having Saskia followed
wasn't your idea.
You might trust her.
I don't even know her.
You came to me. and I offered you help.
so here it is.
Whoever sent that video
used a dark-web SMS gateway.
so they were able to hide their location.
Okay. we're done.
You're on your own now.
I'm sorry. For all of it.
If I let them take me down.
then my enemies win.
You used to believe in me.
I'm not the one who changed.
Stay away from us.
Keep your head in the game. Sylvie.
-Sorry.
-I'm joking.
Huh.
Can I ask you something about Mum?
Of course.
Do you trust her?
Where's this coming from?
Hmm?
If there's something
you want to tell me. sweetheart.
you can.
It's just you and me.
Whatever it is.
you can tell me.
And we'll fix it.
They're gonna kill Dad!
What?
Who is?
Wh…
Sylvie.
Prime Minister.
-How long?
-Expecting to hear from them any time.
I have a Foreign Office
negotiator waiting.
-I'd like to bring them in.
-I'll do the talking.
Are you sure it's wise
to give them that kind of access?
I don't have any cards left.
-They've sent a link.
-Accessing it now.
Oh. thank God.
Abi… Hey.
They've got Agent Mercer.
He's still alive.
"Now we have another hostage."
"You really shouldn't be fucking with us."
"So what's it going to be?"
I need to know who these people are.
Tell me who you are
and why you're doing this.
"No more time. Say goodbye."
Wait. Stop.
Look. don't do this. I… I…
-Let me help you. I can help.
-Prime Minister.
You said wanted my attention. You have it.
I'm here.
Just tell me what your grievance is.
and we can talk about it.
just you and me. no intermediaries.
I'm listening.
"Resign and it's over."
"You can make us all safe.
It's up to you."
Give me more time. Please.
Alex.
I love you.
I love you. and I trust you.
Whoever these people are.
okay. it's their betrayal. not yours.
-I know about the deadline. Get off me!
-Move away from the door.
-I need to speak to my mum.
-She can't talk right now.
-Let me--
-You can't be here right now.
Why don't you go back upstairs?
I'll be with you
in two minutes. okay? Yeah?
"Time's up."
-Dad?
-Sylvie.
No!
Bring him back.
-Sylvie.
-Sylvie. Go upstairs.
-Get away from me!
-Sylvie.
-Get away from me.
This is your fault.
You're killing him!
No! No!
You need to stop this.
These people haven't done anything to you.
This is about my wife. not them.
Please. We have families.
I have a daughter.
So did I.
Noah!
We need to start being honest
with each other.
or every single one of those hostages
are dead.
Someone's threatening me.
They sent a video
during last night's reception
when we were in the room together.
It appeared on my phone.
and then it was gone. No trace.
A video of what?
I can't say.
There are people dying. That's my husband.
What do you mean you can't say?
If you tell me. then I… I can help you.
So that's why you pulled the mission?
We're both being blackmailed.
If I help you get Alex back.
they'll go public
with what they have on me.
and that will be the end of my presidency.
"Whoever these people are.
it's their betrayal. not yours."
What did he mean by that?
That you can only betray someone
who you have an allegiance to.
I think the kidnappers are British.
If we stand together. then we are a force.
If I help you. they'll destroy me.
and there's too much at stake
for my country.
People I care about will get hurt.
Either way. I lose everything. and
you have no part in it?
It's my choice
to save myself and my family.
You need to make your own.
We have a leak.
I have a source
that has given me information
related to your husband.
I understand
that Alex has been taken hostage
with a group of British doctors.
I also know from my source
that you've been given certain demands
in order to secure his safe release.
A military operation was orchestrated
with the French and then shelved.
-Is that true? And if so. why?
-Who's your source?
-I can't say.
-What is it you want?
A closer relationship
with the press office?
Better access to me?
That… that doesn't seem to be my problem.
Any situation like the one you describe
would be classified.
-It's an issue of national security.
-Our lawyers don't see it that way.
It's in the public interest.
Even if it risks the loss
of innocent lives?
Is that confirmation?
According to my source. if it's left
up to you. they're all going to die.
They've shot two already. haven't they?
Our legal team are
clearing this for print.
and the story
will be on tomorrow's front page.
You are. of course.
entitled to give your side of the story.
Would you like to address the allegation.
Prime Minister.
of your husband being used
as leverage to force your resignation?
-No comment.
-You kept this secret from everyone.
You were meant to be the politician
people could trust.
Zadie. Mr. Kingsley's leaving now.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay. Uh…
We'll issue a D-notice to the Times. tell
them it's a matter of national security.
They'll find a way round it.
They'll publish online outside of the UK.
You can't stop him.
But we could get ahead of him.
Make an announcement tonight. Just
put an end to it.
When you say "an end to it."
what are we ending. exactly?
What are you going to say?
The only thing that I can say.
Abigail. you cannot resign.
You cannot give them what they want.
Set it up.
Thank you.
-Okay. on air in five…
-I'm going to stand.
Thank you. Four. three…
Let's go live now
to Downing Street.
Good evening. Prime Minister.
Good evening.
We received a call from your office
requesting the opportunity for you
to address the British public directly.
Hi. it's Abigail. Leave me a message.
and I'll get back to you when I can.
…to apologize
for the haste of all of this.
I hope as I explain the past 36 hours.
you'll understand why I've been forced
into this position.
As some of you may know.
my husband. Alex Anderson.
is part of the charitable organization
Médecins Sans Frontières.
Change the channel.
Put the news on.
What's going on?
He recently
flew to French Guiana
alongside a team of British doctors.
I last spoke with him on Thursday morning.
after which time
I received President Toussaint…
What is she doing?
Were we told about this?
No. The press officer caught it.
This invitation was made
with the intention of negotiating a deal
that would see France
help supply the UK with drugs
to alleviate the acute shortage
we're facing…
We have to stop her.
Call Adomako.
…a deal
with President Toussaint?
Precisely.
Negotiations had begun
when we received the news
that my husband and three other doctors
had been kidnapped.
We received a video on Sylvie's…
on my daughter's phone.
Alex reading out a message
from his captors.
My daughter saw the look
on her father's face. and I…
I don't think she'll ever forget that.
The video was a demand for me
to resign the office of prime minister
in return for the safe release
of Alex and his fellow doctors.
They are targeting me.
They have weaponized my family.
my husband and my daughter.
Everything in my body.
every instinct as a human.
is telling me to give them what they want.
I want my husband back.
and my daughter wants her father back.
But I cannot give in to them
for the sake of my country.
I will not be threatened.
I will not negotiate.
And I will not resign.
Some people might struggle
to understand that.
They might think
that I'm cold or unfeeling.
But these people will stop at nothing.
If I resign.
no one in a position of authority is safe.
No family member. no child. no loved one.
They're all fair game.
And I know that because these individuals
have been bold enough
to blackmail President Toussaint.
She offered military support to retrieve
the doctors from French territory.
but her offer was rescinded
when the captors contacted her.
They made threats.
And do you know
what the kidnappers are using
to try and influence President Toussaint?
Are any of her family in danger?
At this moment in time.
I don't know the details.
except that they have been
tying the hands of the French
to frustrate our attempts
to bring the doctors back home.
As a result. two of Alex's team…
Fuck.
-…have now been murdered.
-What's she doing?
-…British doctor and a local translator.
-Fighting back.
I've informed both of their families.
This isn't just
about forcing me to stand down.
This is a direct attack on our democracy.
an attempt to hinder us.
to destabilize us. and to silence our…
-Hello.
-What is this?
I honestly have no idea.
…than anyone. if…
You're on the ground
for this express reason. No surprises.
-We misjudged Dalton.
-You misjudged her.
If she won't leave.
then it's time to up the ante.
I'm coming home.
…and to me.
that is not an option.
But your husband
could also be a casualty.
That's surely an impossible situation
you find yourself in.
I want more than anything
to have my husband home
and to get the two remaining doctors
back to their families.
But my loyalties are to this country.
I will not allow it to be held to ransom.
And anyone who thinks that I would
has badly underestimated me.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org